Guide to the Four Seasons Restaurant Collection 1959-2019 MS 3151
New-York Historical Society
Four Seasons Restaurant collection
1959-2019
New-York Historical Society
Four Seasons (Restaurant)
MS 3151
18.75 Linear feet in 13 boxes (12 record cartons, 1 flat box) and 5 oversize folders (4 small, 1 medium).
Scrapbooks, ephemera, photographs, renovation files, books, pamphlets, audiovisual materials, and a few objects documenting the history of the Four Seasons, the pioneering restaurant of "New American Cuisine," located at 99 East 52nd Street, Manhattan, from 1959 to 2016. Its spaces, designed by architect Philip Johnson, included the iconic Pool Room and Grill Room—birthplace of the "power lunch"—and gained official New York City interior landmark status in 1989. The Four Seasons moved in 2018 to 42 East 49th Street, where it closed permanently in 2019.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in seven series:
Series I.
Scrapbooks, 1959-2003, 2005-2019, undated
Series II.
Ephemera, 1962-2019, undated
Series III.
Photographs, slides, transparencies, circa 1970s-2015
Series IV.
Renovations (original and new location), 1987-2018
Series V.
Books, pamphlets, and periodicals, 1971-2016, undated
Series VI.
Audiovisual, 1990-2012, undated
Series VII.
Objects, 1995-2018, undated
Historical Note
When it opened in 1959 at 99 East 52nd Street in Manhattan, off Park Avenue, its $4.5 million dollar cost (about $40 million today) made the Four Seasons the most expensive restaurant ever constructed in New York. Under the stewardship of James Beard, the restaurant pioneered what came to be called "New American Cuisine" and is credited with introducing seasonally-changing menus, and American wines, to the nation.
Occupying ground floor space originally intended for an auto showroom in the Seagram Building—the only New York work of International Style exponent Ludwig Mies van der Rohe—the Four Seasons was designed by Philip Johnson and a team of consultants for Restaurant Associates, which managed it with the Bronfman family (owners of the building and of the Seagram Company) through 1973. The restaurant's interiors included two main dining rooms: the Pool Room, where live trees, changed seasonally, marked the corners of a 20-foot-square white marble water feature, and the Grill Room, where rippling chain draperies at the windows complemented artist Richard Lippold's quivering brass rod sculpture suspended over the bar. In 1989 the New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission designated the Four Seasons an interior landmark. (This designation excluded a key decorative feature which hung in the passage connecting the Pool and Grill rooms since the restaurant opened: Pablo Picasso's painted theater curtain for Diaghilev's 1919 ballet "Le Tricorne." Purchased by the Bronfmans for the space, it was given in 2005 to the New York Landmarks Conservancy. Sale of the Seagram Building prompted its removal and conservation in 2014. Custody of the curtain was transferred to the New-York Historical Society, where it remains on display.)
Tom Margittai and Paul Kovi assumed management of the restaurant beginning in 1973, passing control in 1994 to junior partners Julian Niccolini and Alex von Bidder. Under their leadership the Four Seasons played host to countless celebrity regulars, financiers, publishers, politicians, and fashion editors. For decades architect Philip Johnson had his daily private table in the Grill Room, where the concept of the "power lunch"—a working meal over which the rich and powerful discuss important deals—is said to have originated.
Through a change in ownership of the Seagram Building, the Four Seasons lost its lease in 2016, and closed after dinner service on July 16 of that year. In 2018 the restaurant moved a few blocks south to 42 East 49th Street, to a $30 million dollar space designed by Brazilian architect Isay Weinfeld that echoed the décor of its original location. The Four Seasons closed permanently on June 11, 2019.
For further details see John Mariani and Alex von Bidder, The Four Seasons: A History of America's Premier Restaurant (New York: Crown Publishers, 1994), New-York Historical Society library call number F128 TX945 .5 .F45M37 1994.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
The VHS cassettes in Series VI are restricted because of their fragility and because N-YHS has no equipment on which to play them. Similarly, the digital media (i.e., CDs and DVDs), also in Series VI, are currently restricted from access in order to ensure that the digital files are not accidentally corrupted. For further information please contact the curator of manuscripts at manuscripts@nyhistory.org.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection is the gift of Alex von Bidder, co-owner of the Four Seasons from 1994 through 2019. Most of the material arrived in 2019 (accession no. MS-2019-039), except for the files under Series IV, and some of the objects in Series VII, which were received in 2016.
Scope and Contents
Except for two employee handbooks and an in-house operations manual [see Series II], this collection does not include the business records of the Four Seasons. Rather, the material is largely ephemeral in nature. A significant portion is devoted to scrapbooks documenting the years 1959–2003, presumably assembled by the restaurant's public relations staff from newspaper clippings, magazine and trade publication tear sheets, award certificates, photographs, banquet and regular menus, and invitations, all relating to events and people—especially celebrity diners—at the Four Seasons [see Series I].
Assorted ephemera dating from 1962–2019 complements the scrapbooks, and includes printed items, such as wine lists; matchboxes and a shopping bag with the Four Seasons logo; and a menu for President John F. Kennedy's 45th birthday dinner at the restaurant [see Series II].
Photographs document the Four Seasons' spaces, décor, and staff between the 1970s and 2015, with a large portion given to the kitchen renovations undertaken in 1997. Others capture owners Tom Margittai, Paul Kovi, Julian Niccolini, and Alex von Bidder posed with celebrities and world figures who visited the restaurant, such as Anne, Princess Royal, James Beard, George H. W. Bush, Barbara Bush, Bill Clinton, David Frost, Keith Hernandez, Philip Johnson, John F. Kennedy, Sophia Loren, Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Lee Radziwill, Diane von Furstenberg, the Duke and Duchess of Windsor, and the 14th Dalai Lama [see Series III].
The collection contains a series of files on construction and renovation projects at the original (99 East 52nd Street) and final (42 East 49th Street) locations of the Four Seasons between 1987 and 2018; workaday topics include "Asbestos," "Bathroom ADA," "Exhaust," "Ice Machines," and "Plumbing" [see Series IV].
The restaurant's famous food and stylish interiors were featured in numerous books, pamphlets, and periodicals over its six-decade history, and the collection includes a selection of these, such as the Four Seasons Cookbook (1971), Dunbar Fine Furniture of the 1950s (2000), and owner Alex von Bidder's picture book for children, Wiggens Learns His Manners at the Four Seasons Restaurant (2009) [see Series V].
As with print media, the Four Seasons was profiled countless times by television news outlets, such as CNN, and was the setting for reality and scripted programs, like the short-lived 1990s soap "Central Park West" on CBS. The collection includes copies of many of these appearances, as well as wedding ceremonies and receptions held at the restaurant, on VHS cassettes, CDs, and DVDs, dated 1990–2012 [see Series VI].
Lastly, the collection contains a handful of objects associated with the Four Seasons, such as plaques displaying its 2014 Zagat restaurant review rating, and a hard hat with the restaurant's logo from construction of its final home at 42 East 49th Street [see Series VII].
Separated Materials
Some objects from this collection have been transferred to the custody of the New-York Historical Society's museum division, including two neckties, a spool of ribbon, a Four Seasons table lamp, a wooden model of the new Four Seasons restaurant, and seven framed medals awarded to the Four Seasons by the James Beard Foundation and DiRoNa (Distinguished Restaurants of North America).
Restaurants -- New York (State) -- New York.; Award plaques.; Ephemera.; Hard hats.; Menus.; Newspaper clippings.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Shopping bags.; Tear sheets.; Four Seasons (Restaurant); Beard, James, 1903-1985; Johnson, Philip, 1906-2005; Kovi, Paul; Margittai, Tom; Mies van der Rohe, Ludwig, 1886-1969; Niccolini, Julian; Von Bidder, Alex; Bronfman family; Seagram Building (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I. Scrapbooks, 1959-2003, 2005-2019, undated
  Scope and Contents
  Contains newspaper clippings, magazine and trade publication tear sheets, award certificates, photographs, banquet and regular menus, invitations, and ephemera, all relating to events and people—especially celebrity diners—at the Four Seasons.
  Arrangement
  Materials have been removed from their oversized binders and placed into folders following the original chronological order. The scrapbooks proper cover 1959 through 2003; loose material, dating from 1993 through 2019, is filed after. Printed dining menus, where present, are highlighted in the container list.
  - Scrapbook, 1959-1966 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes menus dated
    • 1959 August 14: Just Because Luncheon / Andrew and Leonard Arkin
    • 1962 May 19: President's Birthday Dinner [J.F.K.; photocopy]
    • 1962 August 21: Gorton's of Gloucester, Inc. Introduces the Fresh-Lock Process
    • 1963 June 10: Luncheon to Honor the Honorable Michel Legendre, Consul General of France
    • 1963 October 3: general menu [in pencil on verso: "Emperor Haile Selassie"]
    • 1963 October 18: In Honor of His Majesty King Humbert II of Savoy
    • 1964 March 16: Physician's Wine Appreciation Society
    • 1964 June 16: Un Diner de Convives
    • 1964 August 7: New York Life Welcomes Directors and Wives American Bar Association Endowment
    • 1965 June 9: Africa Service Institute in honour of Mr. John Mosler
    • 1965 June 27: Dinner in honor of Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Weinberger on the occasion of their marriage tendered by Mr. and Mrs. Alex Rutledge
    • 1965 September 1: Reception and Dinner Honoring Mr. Joseph L. Eckhouse
    • 1965 December 1: Reception and Dinner in honor of Dr. and Mrs. A. W. Jann
    • 1965 December 9: Reception and Luncheon tendered by Max M. Fisher
    • 1966 January 26: Charter Members Luncheon Club
    • 1966 April 29: Reception and Dinner
    • 1966 November 6: general menu [in pencil on verso: "Cohen Nathaniel"]
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2-3)
    • 1967 February 1: Dinner in Honor of Charles Henri Heidsieck by Thomas F. McCarthy
    • 1967 March 22: Confrérie de la Chaine des Rotisseurs
    • 1967 June 18: Wedding Reception and Dinner in honor of Mr. and Mrs. Michael Slater
    • 1967 November 16: Physician's Wine Appreciation Society
    • 1967 November 27: The Plimsoll Club
    • 1967 December 12: Confrérie de la Chaine des Rotisseurs
    • 1967 December 19: Le Parlement de Saint Nicolas de la Commanderie de Bordeaux
    • 1968 January 16: Confrérie de la Chaine des Rotisseurs
    • 1968 January 18: Luncheon to Honor Count Michel d'Ornano
    • 1968 February 19: Foods of the World Press Reception
    • 1968 February 29: Reception and Dinner in honor of James E. Aitken
    • 1968 March 20: Dinner to Honor the Delegation from the Finance Committee of the French National Assembly
    • 1968 May 1: Dinner in Honor of Mr. and Mrs. Henri Woltner by Thomas F. McCarthy
    • 1968 May 28: Luncheon to Honor General Georges F. Doriot
    • 1968 June 9: Wedding Reception and Dinner in honor of Doctor and Mrs. Emanuel Marritt
    • 1968 September 6: In Honor of Minx Deutsch and Mel Boren, Pre-nuptial Dinner
    • 1968 September 7: In Honor of Mr. and Mrs. Mel Boren, Wedding Dinner
    • 1968 October 31: Christian Brothers of California Third Annual Wine Harvest Luncheon
    • 1968 December 9: Le Parlement de Saint Nicolas de la Commanderie de Bordeaux
    • 1969 September 11: Confrérie de la Chaine des Rotisseurs
    • 1970 December 17: Le Parlement de Nöel de la Commanderie de Bordeaux
    • 1971 March 11: Four Seasons Grill Room Dinner
    • 1971 April 7: Diner de Gala Taittinger
    • undated: Wine and Food Society, Inc., New York
    • undated: Dinner honoring the Continental Mark IV
  - Scrapbook, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    • 1974 March 12: Fête de Jurade de St. Emilion
    • 1977 June 14: Summer
    • 1977 September 26: Fall
    • 1978 April 5: Spring
    • 1978 June 21: Summer
    • 1978 September 26: Autumn
    • 1979 March 20: Spring
    • 1979 June 20: Summer
    • 1979 October 3: Autumn
    • undated: The Four Seasons Grill (multiple drafts, versions)
    • undated: This Evening's Entrees for the Four Seasons Theatre Dinner
  - Scrapbook, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    • 1980 January 10: Winter
    • 1980 March 27: Spring
    • 1980 June 17: Summer
    • 1980 September 17: Autumn
    • 1981 January 14: Winter
    • 1981 June 23: Summer
    • 1981 September 22: Autumn
    • 1981 December 16: Winter
    • 1982 March 23: Spring
    • 1982 April 22: Spring (at the Dorchester, London)
    • 1982 June 15: Summer
    • 1982 October 12: Autumn
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6-7)
    • 1983 March 16: Spring
    • 1983 June 14: Summer
    • 1983 October 4: Autumn
    • 1984 January 12: Winter
    • 1984 March 21: Spring
    • 1984 June 20: Summer
    • 1984 October 9: Autumn
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8-9)
    • 1985 January 16: Winter
    • 1985 June 13: Summer
    • 1985 October 8: Autumn
    • 1986 January 16: Winter
    • 1986 March 25: Spring
  - Scrapbook, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1993 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1994 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
    • 1994 January 19: Winter Four Seasonal
    • 1994 May 1: Third Annual Dinner Debut of the 1990 Barolo Vintage (invitation + menu)
    • 1994 May 11: Wine Writers Circle 20th Anniversary Luncheon
    • 1994 September 29: Autumn Four Seasonal
    • 1994 October 23: Premiere Showing of the Bordeaux Vintage 1992 (invitation)
  - Scrapbook, 1995 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
    • 1995 February 5: Irvington Institute for Medical Research, Valentine's Day (invitation + menu)
    • 1995 May 1: Fourth Annual Dinner Debut of the 1991 Barolo Vintage (invitation)
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1996 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5-6)
    • 1996 January 30: Winter Four Seasonal
    • 1996 March 26: Spring Four Seasonal
    • 1996 May 6: Fifth Annual Dinner Debut of the 1992 Barolo Vintage (invitation + menu)
  - Scrapbook (3 folders), 1997 January - June (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7-9)
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1997 July - December (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Scrapbook (3 folders), 1998 January - June (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Scrapbook, 1998 June - August (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1998 September - December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Scrapbook (2 folders), 1999 January - May (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Scrapbook (3 folders), 1999 May - September (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9-11)
  - Scrapbook, 1999 October - December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 2000 January - June (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 2000 June - December (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 2001 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 2002 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (3 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5-7)
  - Loose material from scrapbooks, 1993, 1995 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
  - Loose material from scrapbooks (3 folders), 2005-2019, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9-11)
  - Loose material from scrapbooks, circa 1970-2015, undated (Oversize small, Folder 1 of 4)
  - Loose material from scrapbooks, 2016, undated (Oversize medium, Folder 1 of 1)
- Series II. Ephemera, 1962-2019, undated
  A mix of printed items and smaller-sized objects produced by or for the restaurant.
  Organized alphabetically by topic.
  - Bar Room Savories menu, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cooking Class, 2019 March 2 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cooking Class, 2019 May 11 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
  - Employee Handbook, [2018-2019] (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
  - Employment Manual, 1992 July (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
  - JFK 45th birthday (2 folders), 1962 May 19 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17-18)
    The Four Seasons hosted a dinner for John F. Kennedy following the Democratic Party's fundraising gala in his honor at Madison Square Garden, where Marilyn Monroe famously sang "Happy Birthday, Mr. President." Includes layout and table set-up instructions, staff assignments for the evening, and a framed menu.
  - "Lunch Money", [circa 1994-2019] (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
    Small black, canvas, zippered change purse with caricatures of Four Seasons owners Alex von Bidder and Julian Niccolini, containing a gold-toned token with the same images and stamped "LUNCH FOR TWO AT THE BAR / IN JULIAN I TRUST" and "A BOTTLE OF CA' DEL BOSCO / IN ALEX I TRUST."
  - Matchboxes (3), undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
    Conservation note
    Boxes (with Four Seasons logo) retained, and stick matches discarded for safety, January 2020.
  - News Articles, circa 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
  - [Operations manual], [before 2016] (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
    From a binder labeled "Menu."
  - Place cards (blank), undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
  - Press packet, original location, circa 2000 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
  - Press packet, new location (3 copies in 3 folders), [2016] (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7-9)
  - Shopping bag, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    Small, paper doggie bag with cord handles and Four Seasons logo.
  - Stationery, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    Blank stationery designed with caricatures of Julian Niccolini, Alex von Bidder, and other Four Seasons personnel.
  - Wine list, 2005 May 20 (Offsite-box 9, Volume 1)
  - Wine list (incomplete), 2007 October 15 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
  - Wine list (2 copies), 2008 February 12 (Offsite-box 9, Volume 2)
  - Wine list illustrations, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
- Series III. Photographs, slides, transparencies, circa 1970s-2015
  Images of renovations to the Four Seasons kitchen in 1997, the restaurant's 40th anniversary celebration in 1999, and views of its spaces and staff at various events.
  Organized by photographic format: prints, slides, transparencies, and photograph albums.
  - Photographs. Kitchen renovation (8 folders), 1997 January 1-18 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12-19)
  - Photographs. Food preparation and interiors, [circa 1997?] (Offsite-box 5, Folder 20)
  - Photographs. Miscellaneous (3 folders), circa 1970s-2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 21-23)
    Chiefly images of Four Seasons owners Tom Margittai, Paul Kovi, Julian Niccolini, and Alex von Bidder posed with celebrities and world figures who visited the restaurant, such as Anne, Princess Royal, James Beard, George H. W. Bush, Barbara Bush, Bill Clinton, David Frost, Keith Hernandez, Philip Johnson, John F. Kennedy, Sophia Loren, Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Lee Radziwill, Diane von Furstenberg, the Duke and Duchess of Windsor, and the 14th Dalai Lama.
    Contents of Folder 23 treated for mold, January 29, 2020.
  - Photographs. Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-2015 (Oversize small, Folder 2 of 4)
  - Slides. [Restaurant interiors and staff] (2 folders), 1995-1998, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - Slides. [Restaurant interiors] (Daniel Aubry), [2001] (Offsite-box 5, Folder 26)
  - Slides. 40th anniversary (Mary Hilliard), 1999 June 24 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
  - Slides. 40th anniversary (Patrick McMullan), 1999 June 24 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
  - Transparencies. [Kitchen staff] (C. G. Winston), undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photograph album (green binding). Four Seasons. Fred Marcus Photography, undated (Offsite-box 8, Volume 1)
  - Photograph album (brown binding). Gruber Photographers, undated (Offsite-box 8, Volume 2)
  - Photograph album (black binding). Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 8, Volume 3)
- Series IV. Renovations (original and new location), 1987-2018
  Files documenting renovations and construction at the original (99 East 52nd Street) and final (42 East 49th Street) locations of the Four Seasons.
  - Renovations: A, 1995-1997 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    From hanging files labeled
    • Authorization
    • Architects: bills
    • Architects: contracts & agreements
    • Architects: proposals
    • Asbestos: proposals
    • Asbestos: reports
    • AVB [Alex von Bidder]: renovation notes
  - Renovations: B, 1992-1996 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
    • Bathroom: ADA
    • Braun Equipment Company
    • Broiler
  - Renovations: Bake Shop (3 folders), 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6-8)
  - Renovations: C, 1987-2011 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
    • Canopy: correspondence & reports; proposals; schedules
    • Canopy: sign
    • Carpet
    • Cold Food Preparation / Coffee Station
    • Construction Manager (TECOR)
  - Renovations: E-I, 1992-2011 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
    • Electrical
    • Elevator
    • Engineers
    • Exhaust
    • Belmont Freeman
    • Furniture
    • Ice Machines
    • Inspection (Dept. of Buildings)
  - Renovations: K, 1995-1997 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
    • Kitchen: bills; contracts / agreements; correspondence & reports
    • Kitchen: equipment; estimates
    • Kitchen Facilities Renovation
  - Renovations: L, 1996-1999 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 12)
    • Landmarks [i.e., New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission]
    • Loading Dock
    • Locker Room
  - Renovations: M, 1996-2001 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 13)
    • Maintenance Contracts
    • Metal Refinishing
  - Renovations: O, 2000 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
    • Office Restoration
    • Operating & Maintenance Manuals [for] Food Service Equipment
  - Renovations: P (2 folders), 1988-2002 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2-3)
    • Pending Maintenance
    • Picasso Cleaning
    • Plants (foliage)
    • Plumbing
    • Point of Sale -- Remanco
    • Pool
  - Renovations: Project Manual, 1996 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
  - Renovations: Restoration Budget, 1996 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
  - Renovations: S, 1998-2009 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    • Sciame Construction
    • Stonhard
  - Renovations: T-W, 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
    • Tecor
    • Telephone Door
    • Woodwork
  - New location. Corey Di Stasio Design. Four Seasons Restaurant Code Signage Design Development, 2018 March 9 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
  - New location. Mark Ladner & Michael Wilson. Four Seasons Summary & Direction Notes, [2018] (Offsite-box 7, Folder 9)
  - New location. Isay Weinfeld architectural designs, 2016-2017 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 10)
  - New location. Isay Weinfeld architectural designs, 2016-2017 (Oversize small, Folder 3 of 4)
  - New location. HMWhite. Four Seasons North & South Terrace Preliminary Planting Palette, 2017 March 23 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 11)
  - New location. HMWhite. Four Seasons North & South Terrace Preliminary Planting Palette, 2018 (Oversize small, Folder 4 of 4)
  - New location. Gel with Four Seasons trees logo, circa 2016-2018 (Offsite-box 9, Tube 1)
    Two colored transparent sheets.
- Series V. Books, pamphlets, and periodicals, 1971-2016, undated
  Contains publications relating in some way to the Four Seasons restaurant, its food, decor, and history.
  Organized chronologically by publication date.
  - Charlotte Adams. The Four Seasons Cookbook, 1971 (Offsite-box 10, Volume 1)
  - One Hundred Seasons (2 copies), [1984] (Offsite-box 10, Volume 2)
  - Martha Stewart. Weddings, 1987 (Offsite-box 10, Volume 3)